Guide to the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6 Records WAG.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Editor's Files.
  - Fallsburg, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Fortune Magazine Articles, 1944-1971 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Grossman, Mildred, 1938-1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - "Growth of a Union", 1930-1944 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - History, 1939; 1952-1964 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Hotel Closings, 1964-1968 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Hotel Industry: Articles, undated (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Hotel Industry: History, 1960-1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Hotel Voice: General, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Impartial Chairman, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Job Placement Office, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Joe's Restaurant, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1957-1963 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - King's Hamburgers, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Labor Day, 1958-1971 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Labor History, 1963-1981 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Lane, Gertrude, 1937-1953 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Liquor Tax, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Local Joint Board, 1944-1952 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Local 6: History, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Local 6: History, 1930s (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Local 6: History, 1940s (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Local 6: History, 1950s (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Local 32A: Building Services Employees, 1932-1939 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Local 32A: Building Services Employees, 1940-1945 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Printing, 1971-1984 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Randorf, William, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Restaurants: General, 1962-1966 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Social Security, 1955-1967 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Valentin, Gerena, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Series VIII: Membership Records, 1938-1961; 1975.
  - D1-D1800; D3901-D4500 [Individual items numbers refer to "Ledger Page"], 1938-1939 (Box 35)
  - D4501-D6000; D8401-D9300, 1939-1942 (Box 36)
  - D9301-D11400, 1942-1943 (Box 37)
  - D11401-D13500, 1943-1944 (Box 38)
  - D13501-D15600, 1944-1945 (Box 39)
  - D15601-D16200; D31400-D33402, 1945; 1958-1960 (Box 40)
  - H3307-H3600; H4801-H6900, 1939-1941 (Box 41)
  - H11400-H13800, 1943 (Box 42)
  - H15601-H17700, 1944-1945 (Box 43)
  - H17701-H20100, 1945-1946 (Box 44)
  - H20100-H21300; H26101-H27300, 1946; 1948 (Box 45)
  - H27301-H30000, 1948-1950 (Box 46)
  - H30001-H30600; H35251-H36499, 1950; 1954-1955 (Box 47)
  - K1-K2400, 1938-1939 (Box 48)
  - K2401-K23600 (incomplete), 1939-1940; 1956 (Box 49)
  - K23601-K25699; B33-B28263, 1956-1961 (Box 50)
  - Dues List (by club): Racquet and Tennis, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Dues List (by club): Recess, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Dues List (by club): River, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Dues List (by club): Royal Globe, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Dues List (by club): Sixty East, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Dues List (by club): Sky, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Dues List (by club): Stock Exchange, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Dues List (by club): Traffic, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Dues List (by club): Union, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Dues List (by club): University, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Dues List (by club): Wall Street, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Dues List (by club): Weavers, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dues List (by club): Whitehall, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Dues List (by club): Williams, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Dues List (by club): Yacht (aka New York Yacht), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Dues List (by club): Yale, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Delegate List: By Name, Jul 21, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Delegate List: By Name, Jul 21, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Delegate List: By Shop, Oct 14, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Delegate List: By Shop, Feb 10, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Local 69: New Jersey Shops Per Capita Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Membership Roster, May 1, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Membership Survey [Restricted until 2034], 1994 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Quality Inn: Severance Forms [Restricted until 2035], 1985 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Membership Reports: Loews [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
  - Membership Reports: Waldorf Astoria [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
  - Membership Reports: Sheraton [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
  - Membership Reports: Regency [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
  - Membership Reports: Hilton and Towers [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
  - Membership Reports: Essex House [Restricted until 2035], 1995 (Box 53)
- Series IX: Addendum, General Files.
  - Abbey Victoria, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Activity/ Expenses Reports (C. Anthony), 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - AFL-CIO: 14th Constitutional Convention, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO: Organizing Education Workshops, "Building the Labor Movement; Organizing to Win", 1996 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO: Organizer's Guide, [1990] (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Agreements, 1952-1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Agreements, 1978;1985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Agreements, Jun 26, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Alden Hotel: Grievances, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Alden Owners, Inc.: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Algonquin Hotel: Incentive Guidelines, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Allied Workers' Union of South Africa: Correspondence, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Amalgamation of Locals 6, 22, 69, and 1, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Americana Hotel, 1969;1977 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Americana Hotel: Grievances, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Anthony, Charles A.: Central Labor Council, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Anthony, Charles A.: Notes, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Anti-Communist Flyer (Anti-Rubin and Local 6), Oct (Box 54, Folder 17a)
  - Apartment House Strike, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Applications for Membership [Restricted], 1984 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Arbitrator Dispute (Impartial Chairman Cass), 1986 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Arcos, Arcadio, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Article 28: Appeals for Relief, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Astor Hotel: Grievances, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Bankers' Club of America, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Banquet Committee, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Banquet Department: Dance, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Banquet Job Statistics, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Banquet Staff, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Barbizon Hotel: Bargaining, 1994 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Barclay, The, 1977-1979 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Bargaining, 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Bargaining, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Bartenders' International League of America: Report of the Secretary Treasurer, Aug 1899-Nov 1899 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Benefits, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Benefits, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Berkeley Owners Corp., 1997 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Berkshire Hotel, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - Biltmore, The, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - Black-Out Day, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Board Meeting Schedules, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - Board Room Club: Agreement, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Brook, The, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - Brook, The: Bargaining, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Brook, The: Bargaining, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Brooklyn Club: Agreement, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Building: 140 West 43rd Street, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - Building: 708-709 8th Avenue, Mar 1978- Feb 1981 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Business Agent Assignments, [1977; 1979] (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Business Agent Assignments, [1990] (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Business Agent Assignments, [1991] (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - Business Agent Assignments, 2000 (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Business Agents: Car Allowance, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Business Agents: Guidelines, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Business Agents: Joe Melendez and Carter Best, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Business Agents: Officer of the Day, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - By-Laws, 1967; 1973; 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - By-Laws: Amendments, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - By-Laws: Committee Rosters, [1977] (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - By-Laws: New York Hotel Trades Council, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Cafeteria Industry Welfare Plan, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - Canadian Club, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - Carlton House: Agreements, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - Carlyle Hotel, 1977; 1979 (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - Carlyle Hotel, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - Carlyle Hotel: Grievances, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - Carlyle Hotel: Tips, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - Carter Hotel, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - Celebrity Deli: Agreements, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - Celebrity Deli: Contract, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - Center for Career Studies (Empire State College): Union Leadership/ College Degree Program, Oct 21, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - Central Labor Relations Council of New York, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - Century Association: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - Century Association: Discrimination Case, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - Cerebral Palsy, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - Chemists' Club, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - Citicorp Club, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - City Athletic Club: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - City Squire Hotel: Grievances, 1974;1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - City-Wide Blackout, Jul 14, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - Closures: Hotels and Restaurants, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - Cloud Club, 1974-1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Cloud Club, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Club Department, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Club Department: Agreements, 1994-1996 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Club Department: Agreements, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Club Department: Bargaining/ Agreements, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Club Department: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Club Department: Grievances and Complaints, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Club Employees Pension Fund, 1977-1980 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Club Management Co, Inc., 1975;1978 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Clubs: Dues, Check-off Lists, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Clubs: Statistics and Trends, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Colony Club: Agreement, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Committee For Trade Union Democracy, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Commodore Hotel: Grievances, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Common Ground Community HDFC: Agreement, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Complaints, 1965-1969 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Complaints, 1991-1993 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Compliance Audit Program, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Consortium for Workers Education, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Contract Highlights, 1990-1995 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Contributions, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Convention, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Cooperative for American Relief Everywhere- Nicaragua, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Club: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Cornell University (New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations), 1962-1992 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence: Anthony, Charles A., 1979-1989 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: International, 1982-1985 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: Kamaras, Vangel, 1967;1974-1980 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence: Marley, James, 1967-1973 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Pavlista, Lubos, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Pitta, Vito, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Cosmopolitan Club: Bargaining, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Craft Meetings, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Daily News Strike, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Days Inn, 1985;1986 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Deduction of Dues Authorization, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Defense Fund, 1981-1985 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Delegate Assembly: General, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Delegate Assembly: Rosters, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Delegate Handbooks, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Delegate List: By Name [Restricted], Jul 21. 1988 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Delegate List: By Shop [Restricted], 1987 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Delegate Meetings: Notices, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Delegate Training Program, 1962;1963 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Delmonico: Grievances, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialists of America: Youth Internship Program, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Disability Claims, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Discrimination Charges, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Dissident Groups: Rank-and-File Membership Party, 1958-1968 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Doral Park Ave. Hotel, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Doral park Ave. Hotel: Wrongful Termination of Alfred Kerbel (legless cashier), May 1978- Jun 1978 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Doral Restaurants: Bargaining, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Doral Tuscany Towers, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Doubles Club: Grievances, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Downtown Association, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Downtown Association: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Drake Hotel, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Drake Hotel: Bargaining, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Drake Hotel: Grievances, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Drake Hotel: Petition against Eye Identification System, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Drake Hotel: Shepheard's Restaurant, Lay-Offs, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Dues, 1981-1983 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Dues, 1987-1990 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Dues Increase, Mar 1978- Apr 1978 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Dues Increase/ Medical Plan Flyer, [1950] (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Dues Increase: Referendum, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Dues Payments: Listed by Local, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Dumont Plaza Hotel: Bargaining, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Eastern Airline Strike, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Edison Rivera, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Education: Class for Executive Board Members and Shop Chairmen, [1945] (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Elections, Administrative: Campaigning, "Vote for These Administrative Candidates, [1950] (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Elections, Convention: Delegates, 1945-1997 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Elections, General: Ballot, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Elections, General: Club Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Elections, General: District 1 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Elections, General: District 2 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Elections, General: District 2 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Elections, General: District 3 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Elections, General: District 4 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Elections, General: District 5 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - Elections, General: District 6 Acceptances and Declinations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - Elections, General: Election and Objections Committee Minutes, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Elections, General: Nominees, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - Elections General: Nominations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - Elections, General: Preparations, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Elections, General: Registrars and Watchers, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Elections, General: Election and Objections Committee Minutes, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Elections, General: Election Breakdown, May 19, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Elections, General: Election Day Expenses, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Elections, General: Hotel Breakdown, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Elections, General: Nominations and Rejects Under Art. IV, Sec 7a(2) of By-Laws, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Elections, General: Membership Breakdown, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Elections, General: Opposition Slate Nominations, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - Elections, General: Preparations, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 53)
  - Elections, General: Special Election Editions of the Hotel and Club Voice, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 54)
  - Elections, General: Wirtz Suit Against Local 6 in Violation of Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act, 1965 (Box 56, Folder 55)
  - Elections, General: Flyer (Route A, District 1), 1971 (Box 56, Folder 56)
  - Elections, General: Installation of Officers, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 57)
  - Elections, General: Flyers, 1941;1947; 1959 (Box 56, Folder 58)
  - Elections, General: Forms and Flyers, 1962;1964; 1968 (Box 56, Folder 59)
  - Elections, General: Installation Ceremonies, 1968;1991; 1997 (Box 56, Folder 60)
  - El Salvador Earthquake Relief, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 61)
  - Embassy, Hotel, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 62)
  - Empire State Club: Agreements, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 63)
  - Employment Report (Unemployment Problem), Jan 1949 (Box 56, Folder 64)
  - Equal Pay Act, [1977] (Box 56, Folder 65)
  - Ernst, Hugo (re: article on "The Negro Question"), 1942 (Box 56, Folder 66)
  - Essex House: Correspondence, 1975;1977 (Box 56, Folder 67)
  - Essex House: Grievances, 1973; 1976; 1979 (Box 56, Folder 68)
  - Executive Board Communications, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 69)
  - Executive and Assembly Boards: Attendance, Dec 1986- Mar 1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Nominees, [1950] (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 50th Anniversary: Congratulatory Letters, etc., 1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Finances: Investments, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Finances: Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Finances: Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Finances: Statement of Assets, Delayed Check-Off, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Floor Steward Classification, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Flyer: "Where Do Your Due Dollars Go?", 1953 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Four Seasons: Organizing, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Friars Club, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - George Washington, Hotel, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Gertrude Lane Memorial Scholarships, 1974-1976 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Gertrude Lane Memorial Scholarships, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Gideon Putnam Hotel, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Golden Tulip Barbizon Hotel: Grievances, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Gotham Hotel, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Grand Café, 1977;1978 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Grand Hyatt Hotel (Regency Lexington Partners): Agreement, Jun 1, 1985 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Grand Hyatt Hotel: Banquet Waiters, 1985-1989 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Grand Hyatt Hotel: Cerebral Palsy Fund, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Grand Hyatt Hotel: Las Vegas Hilton Strike, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Greenbaum, Isadore (Banquet Waiter), 1977 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Greyhound Strike, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Grievance Board Cases, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Grievance Board Cases, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Grievance Board Cases, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Grievance Board Cases, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Grievance Board Cases, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Grievances, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Grievances, Apr 1980- Jan 1981 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Grievances and Arbitration Process Outline, [1995] (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Grievances: Impartial Chairman Decisions, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Grievances: Impartial Chairman Lubos Pavlista (I), 1977-1979 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Grievances: Impartial Chairman Lubos Pavlista (II), 1977-1979 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Grievance Statistical Reports, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Hampshire House, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Hampshire House: Bargaining, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Harley Hotel, 1980-1985 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Harmonie Club, 1984-1985 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Harmonie Club: Agreements, 1981;1984 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Harmonie Club: Arbitrations, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Harmonie Club: Bargaining, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Harvard Club, 1950; 1984- 1985 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Club: Agreements, 1977-1978; 1996 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Club: Arbitrations, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Club: Grievances, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Hayden Hall, 1980; 1984 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Health Center and Medical Fund: Reports, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Hearings: Delayed Check-offs, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Helmsley Palace: Grievances, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Henry Hudson Hotel, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Hilton Inn at JFK, 1977;1978; 1983 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Hilton, New York, 1975-1999 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Hispanic Labor Committee (NYC CLC), 1988-1990 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Holiday Inn, Coliseum, 1974; 1979 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Holiday Inn, Coliseum: Complaints of Discrimination (Fernandez-Brown Case), 1973-1979 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Holiday Inn, La Guardia Airport, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Holland Hotel, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees' International Alliance, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employees' International Alliance: "The Catering Industry," Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Hotel Association, 1967-1978 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Hotel Association: Membership Roster, Sep 1992 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - HERE: Constitution, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - HERE: Conventions, Preparations, and Proceedings, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - HERE: Conventions, Report and Resolutions, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - HERE: Federal Audit, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - HERE: Finances, Nov 1980- Apr 1981 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - HERE: Finances, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - HERE: General, Jul 1978; 1980s (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - HERE: Jurisdiction, etc., 1975-1977 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - HERE: Local 610 (Puerto Rico), 2000 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Hotel Tax, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Howard Johnson Restaurant-JFK: Grievances, 1978;1991 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Human Rights Appeal Board (Sammy Gibbs vs. New York Hilton), 1977 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Impartial Chairman Hearings, Jul 1996 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - India House, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Initiation Fee Referendum, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Insurance Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Insurance Fund: Reports, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Insurance Fund: Reports, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Intercontinental, 1991-1995 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - International Brotherhood of Switchboard Operators Division, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters: Marriot Marquis Boycott, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - International Hotel: Banquet Waiters, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - International Hotel: Banquet Waiters, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Israel Bonds, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Jackson, Jesse: Campaign Contributions, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Jamaica's Hurricane Victims, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Jerral Enterprises (Metro Delicatessen), 1996 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - JFK Hilton: Emergency Delegate Meeting (Transcript), Mar 28, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - JFK Inn: "Me Too" Agreement, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Joint Legislative Meeting (Workers Comp. Board), May 21, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Joseph Zaffy Memorial Fund, Jul 18, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Kamaras, Vangel: Greek Trade Union Movement, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Kennedy Inn, 1984;1986 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - Kenny's Steak Pub, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - Kew Motor Inn: Sex Discrimination Charge, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - King's Inn, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - Kitano Hotel: Organizing, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 57)
  - Knickerbocker Club: Bargaining, 1977;1995 (Box 58, Folder 58)
  - Knickerbocker Club: Contract, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - Labor Day Parades, 1984;1985; 1987 (Box 58, Folder 60)
  - Labor Day Parades, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 61)
  - "Labor for Liberty": Collections, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 62)
  - Labor Management Advisory Committee (NYC), 1977 (Box 58, Folder 63)
  - Labor's Legislative Priorities Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Lachmann Food Services: Dues, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - La Différence, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - La Folie, 1976;1977 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - La Folie: Severance Pay, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Lambs' Club, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Lancaster Hotel, 1971;1979 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Lawyers Club, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Lay-Offs: Hotels, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 9)